cypress.com 2014-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Cypress

**Privacy Policy**  

**Cypress Semiconductor Data Privacy Policy**

Your right to privacy is very important. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. We believe this information should only be used to help us provide you with better service. That's why we have put a policy in place to protect your personal information. Below is a summary of Cypress's online privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy Summary** ****

This privacy policy tells you about Cypress’s policies and practices for the collection, use, processing, storage, and disclosure of information that we collect about you through our sites and services, including the Web site, www.cypress.com. Before using our sites and services, you will be asked to provide your authorization and consent, agreeing to the terms of this privacy policy and consenting to the processing of information about you as described here. The collection, use, storage, and disclosure of your personal data will be strictly limited to the terms for which you provide your authorization. For the purpose of this policy, the reference to personal data includes the term “personally identifiable information.” 

Cypress complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Additionally, Cypress is committed to full compliance with all relevant country-specific data privacy laws, which include unambiguous authorizations and consents, model contracts/transfer agreements, privacy principles, privacy statements, privacy policies, and country-specific registrations and filings. This privacy policy covers the Web site [www.cypress.com](http://www.cypress.com/).  If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact Cypress through our privacy email at privacy@cypress.com.

**Information That We Collect and Use**

Your right to privacy is very important. In general, when you visit our web sites and access information you remain anonymous. We do require some personal information to enable you to access specialized areas of our site. However, we will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your explicit consent. Typically, all that's requested is your name, e-mail address and some basic information about you, such as job function and contact information. There are occasions where we will ask for additional information. We do this to be able to better understand your needs and provide you with services that we believe may be valuable to you. We also give you the opportunity to elect not to receive materials from us. If you sign up for a Cypress electronic newsletter or e-mail list, each message will include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from that list. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. That's why we have put a policy in place to protect your personal information. 

We may collect personal information from you when you request information from us about our products, services and events. Examples of personal information are name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, company name, and so on. For a complete list of all data elements that we collect and the use of those data elements, contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com). The collection of this data is voluntary on your part, however, in order to provide the information you request, we will need your contact details, most importantly, your email address.

We also may collect personal data about those who communicate with us such as e-mail address, user-specific information on what pages visitors access or visit, and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and site registrations. This information is used to personalize our communications with you about products that are specific to your needs and interests. Rather than burden you with information that is not relevant or of interest to you, we try to target information that is specifically important to you. No personal data is collected, used, accessed, stored, or distributed without your explicit authorization. At any time, even after you have given authorization, you can opt out of receiving these communications by contacting us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com) or clicking on our “unsubscribe link.”

We use the information that we collect to improve the content of our Web pages by incorporating information that is relevant to our clients, to notify customers about updates to our Web site, to contact customers for marketing purposes that are related specifically to their needs and interests, and to track applicants for career opportunities. This information is not shared with other organizations for any reason, commercial or business, without your prior explicit consent. 

If you browse and/or apply for jobs in the Careers portion of our Web site, your application and any additional information that you provide may be used to assess your skills and interests against career opportunities at Cypress, and for reporting purposes as may be required by U.S. law. This usage is covered in the initial authorization that you provide to Cypress. When you access our Recruitment Site, you are asked to provide your authorization for us to collect, use, process, store, and distribute your personal data before you enter any personal data. We use your information to communicate with you and to inform you of career opportunities. 

Cypress does use third-party entities to provide valuable services on our behalf. To provide these services to you, we need your explicit consent to share your personal data with them. Third parties with which we share your information are bound by all relevant data privacy laws, terms of confidentiality, our data privacy model clauses and contractual agreements, and this privacy policy. For a complete list of these third parties and the services they provide, contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com).

Cypress supplements the data it collects with additional data received from third-party sources, by using data append services. The additional supplemental data consists of contact, company, and industry data, as well as title, department, address, phone number, and updated e-mail addresses. For additional information about supplemental data and the third-party sources, contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com).

The company does not share, sell, rent, or trade personal data with third parties for their promotional purposes or for any purposes without your explicit consent. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, click unsubscribe on our web site or contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com). Cypress follows country-specific requirements to implement the opt-out within the legally allowed time period.

Cypress also offers a partial opt-out option. This option allows you to choose the data elements you want to provide and those you do not. For more information about opting out of providing certain data elements, contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com).

If you supply us with your postal address online, as well as your consent, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information about new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive such mailings at any point after your consent has been given, let us know by writing to us at the postal address at the end of this document or by contacting us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com). Send us your name and address and we will remove your name from all lists that we use internally and/or share with other noncommercial organizations. Cypress follows country-specific requirements to implement the opt-out within the legally allowed time periods.

If you give us your telephone number online, and provide consent, you may receive telephone calls from us with information about new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive such telephone calls at any point after giving your consent, write to us at the postal address at the end of this document, or contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com). Send us your name and phone number and we will remove your name from all lists that we use internally and/or share with other noncommercial organizations. Cypress follows country-specific requirements to implement the opt-out within the legally allowed time periods.

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

Customers and applicants can prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected and for which consent was given by contacting us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com).

Upon request, Cypress offers visitors the ability to have their information deleted or corrected for inaccuracies. To have your information corrected, write to us at the address at the end of this document, or contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com). We will respond to your request within the country-specific time frames, which can range from 5 to 30 business days.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain name, but not the e-mail address. 

**Third-Party Technical Support**

Cypress uses the services of third parties to provide technical support services, including customer and field support. All of our third party partners are required to be Safe Harbor Certified and most comply with all relevant country-specific data privacy laws.  For a complete list of our third-party providers please contact [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com). 

**Tell a Friend, Import Contacts**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we ask you for your friend’s name and e-mail address. You may supply that information only if you have the consent of the individual whose name and e-mail address you are providing. (Cypress highly recommends that you provide your friend with our contact information and ask that they contact us directly.) Cypress automatically sends your friend a one-time e-mail message inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store this information.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date and time stamp, and clickstream data. This data is not considered personal data because it does not identify individual users. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

**Cookies**

Propensity management is the management of an individual’s inclination or natural tendency toward certain interests, products, needs, and so on. In order to tailor our communications with you to make sure that we are addressing your specific needs and not overwhelming you with unwanted information, we use cookies to handle propensity management. A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your Web browser. When you revisit [cypress.com](http://www.cypress.com/) our server recognizes the cookie, giving us information about your last visit. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you can opt out, but can still use most of the features of our Web site, including purchasing items. 

This privacy statement covers the use of propensity management by this site only and does not cover the use of propensity management by any advertisers. We work with companies that use third-party cookies and Web beacons to collect anonymous information that helps us measure and improve our content and advertising effectiveness. Our third party partners collect and analyze anonymous usage and volume statistical information from our users. This data is collected only in aggregate form.

**Web Beacons, Web Bugs**

We employ software technology known as Web beacons or Web bugs that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web beacons and Web bugs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies that are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, Web beacons and Web bugs, which are about the size of a period, are embedded invisibly on Web pages. We do not tie the information gathered to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We use third parties to provide services on our site such as e-mail service providers, Web content delivery providers, chat providers, community platform providers, Web employment opportunity providers, product training providers, and sales lead tracking providers. When you sign up for these services, we share your personal information with the third party as necessary to provide that service. For a complete list of these service providers and the services they perform on behalf of Cypress, contact us at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com).

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

**Links to Other Sites**

Cypress Web sites contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Cypress. Although we do not share your personal data with these other sites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Cypress Web sites.

**Security**

The security of your personal data is important to us. When you enter personal data on any Cypress Web site, we encrypt that information by using secure socket layer (SSL) technology.

We follow generally accepted industry standards such as firewalls and encryption and data privacy legal requirements to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and after we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, although we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy page, to the Cypress homepage, and to other places that we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, who has access to it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Us**

Cypress welcomes comments and questions on this policy. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information, and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information secure. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you can contact the Legal Department at the following address or phone number.

**Cypress Semiconductor  
198 Champion Ct.  
San Jose, CA 95134-1709 **

We can be reached via our privacy email at [privacy@cypress.com](mailto:privacy@cypress.com) or by telephone at +1 800-541-4736 and ask to be directed to the Legal Department.
